http://www.businessvoice.com/privacy-policy

Menu
On Hold Marketing
BusinessVoice On Hold MarketingOn Hold Marketing of the MonthHumor On Hold™Multi-Location OrganizationsAffiliate ProgramsCase StudiesVoIPVoice DemosMusic DemosHold Time CalculatorWhy You Need OHMFacts & FiguresWhy We're Better
Additional Solutions
Caller Experience AuditBusinessVoice News NetworkTelephone Skills TrainingSonic Branding / Audio LogosRadio CommercialsCXSelect
About Us
We're UniqueDiscovery & CreativeProactive UpdatingOHM ProductionAssociationsReviewsMadAveGroupTHE Complete On Hold Marketing GuideOur ProcessOur PeopleWe're A Marketing PartnerAgency Partnerships
AwardsBlogs
BusinessVoice BlogThe Director's CutBusinessVoice NewsBVNN Stories
Our Commitment To Privacy
We respect your privacy. That’s why we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This notice is available on our homepage and at every point where personal information may be requested.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the BusinessVoice website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
NameAddressEmail addressPhone number
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
You can register with our website if you would like to receive updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website.
Finally, we never use or share the personal information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Children's Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personal information that we collect online and maintain by emailing This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personal information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 800/473-9000 or send an email to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
Please click the back button to return to the previous page.
THE Complete On Hold Marketing Guide is an expert approach to creating and implementing a successful OHM program.
Our free guide will teach you how to:
Capitalize on the time your customers spend on hold.
Engage your callers with valuable content that moves them to action.
Strengthen your brand identity.
Enter your information to download the free PDF.
Please let us know your name.
Please let us know your email address.
© 2020 BusinessVoice. All rights reserved.
Contact
Privacy Policy
Sitemap
